<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Ashley Martson Archives - The Hollywood Gossip</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/stars/ashley-martson/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/stars/ashley-martson/</link>
	<description>Celebrity Gossip and Entertainment News</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:19:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2024/07/cropped-THG-LOGO-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Ashley Martson Archives - The Hollywood Gossip</title>
	<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/stars/ashley-martson/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Suspected Burglar of Ashley Martson&#8217;s Salon Also Arrested for Homicide, 90 Day &#8230;</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/05/suspected-burglar-of-ashley-martsons-salon-also-arrested-for-homicide-90-day-fiance-alum-reveals/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/05/suspected-burglar-of-ashley-martsons-salon-also-arrested-for-homicide-90-day-fiance-alum-reveals/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:19:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/?p=476172</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 4</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span>Early this year, we reported that someone robbed Ashley Martson&#8217;s salon, breaking in and ransacking the place. The 90 Day &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/05/suspected-burglar-of-ashley-martsons-salon-also-arrested-for-homicide-90-day-fiance-alum-reveals/">Suspected Burglar of Ashley Martson&#8217;s Salon Also Arrested for Homicide, 90 Day &hellip;</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 4</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span>
<p>Early this year, we reported that someone <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/02/ashley-martson-robbed-during-hair-salon-break-in/">robbed Ashley Martson&#8217;s salon</a>, breaking in and ransacking the place.</p>



<p>The <em>90 Day Fiance</em> alum was fairly quiet after the incident, likely hoping to not interfere with the case against the burglar.</p>



<p>Now, the suspect is facing more than just burglary charges.</p>



<p>David Brian Hartsook is also accused of the shooting death of a security guard.</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">David Brian Hartsook, seen here in this mugshot, is facing multiple criminal charges in Pennsylvania, including a somewhat famous burglary. Police also charge him with the shooting death of a security guard.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (Berks County Prison)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>&#8220;Remember the guy who robbed my salon?&#8221; Ashley Martson asked her fans and followers on Tuesday.</p>



<p>&#8220;He killed someone,&#8221; she announced.</p>



<p>She linked to a news story about Hartsook&#8217;s alleged shooting, in which one security guard died and another suffered injuries.</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">On Tuesday, May 23, Ashley Martson told her followers that the suspect in the burglary of her salon was also facing a murder charge. <span class="image-caption-credit"> (Instagram)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>Hartsook is facing charges over the shooting homicide of a security guard in Berks County.</p>



<p>However, he allegedly created a series of crimes in and around York County.</p>



<p>One of those more local crimes was the burglary and ransacking of her salon in Springettsbury Township (yes, that&#8217;s its real name).</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">In early February of 2023, Ashley Martson shared security footage of the burglary of her salon.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (Instagram)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>Back in early February, Ashley took to social media to seek the help of the public in identifying those who broke in.</p>



<p>She even shared security camera video (which we, at the time, converted to a GIF for your convenience) of the perpetrators.</p>



<p>Though Ashley later deleted the post (perhaps at the request of authorities on the case), she did not have to wait long.</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">In her Instagram caption, Ashley Martson sought the public&#8217;s assistance in identifying the burglars who ransacked her salon.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (Instagram)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>Just two days following the burglary, Springettsbury Township Police identified their suspects.</p>



<p>The investigators arrested both David and Richard Hartsook and charged the brothers with burglary and theft.</p>



<p>All of that went down in just the first few days of February. By May, there was a twist.</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img decoding="async" width="1024" height="596" src="https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-1024x596.png" alt="" class="wp-image-332628" srcset="https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-1024x596.png 1024w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-300x175.png 300w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-768x447.png 768w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-735x428.png 735w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-335x195.png 335w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-347x202.png 347w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-520x303.png 520w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-640x373.png 640w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-960x559.png 960w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce-1080x629.png 1080w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/07/ashley-martson-wants-a-divorce.png 1297w" sizes="(max-width: 760px) calc(100vw - 20px), 720px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">During her time on 90 Day Fiance, Ashley Martson had many opportunities to express disappointment, frustration, and heartbreak.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (TLC)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>Last week, Berks County officials charged David Hartsook with first-degree murder.</p>



<p>Police arrested him at his home in York City.</p>



<p>(He was out on bail following the burglary of Ashley&#8217;s salon and also another theft case. The guy allegedly loves crimes!)</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">During one weird scandal, Ashley Martson felt the need to &#8220;prove&#8221; things, including her medical history, to fans who had latched onto conspiracy theories.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (Instagram)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>Allegedly, Hartsook opened fire upon two private security officers on August, 2022.</p>



<p>The two were on patrol in Morgantown, Berks County.</p>



<p>It sounds like investigators believe that he was in the process of sealing catalytic converters from vehicles when the security offers, doing their jobs, caught him in the act.</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">Despite having (once again) broken up with her then-husband, and not for the last time, Ashley Martson modeled for a bridal photoshoot. Life can be weird sometimes.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (Instagram)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>37-year-old Troy Rickenbach died in the shooting.</p>



<p>His partner, 43-year-old Rafael Yambo, sustained injuries.</p>



<p>That is heartbreaking to hear. For both men and especially for Rickenbach&#8217;s loved ones.</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">After her initial post, Ashley Martson continued to communicate with fans and followers about her burglarized salon.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (Instagram)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>We mentioned that Hartsook was on bail for the burglary <em>and </em>for another theft when police arrested him last week.</p>



<p>The other crime went down just two months after that shooting.</p>



<p>On September 29 of last year, he allegedly stole a $100 trash can. Literally just drove up in a ban, grabbed the handle, and kept driving, eventually tossing the garbage bin into the van. A man who lived on the street saw the whole thing and wrote down the license number.</p>


<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">For many episodes of 90 Day Fiance, Ashley Martson was straight-up not having a good time.<span class="image-caption-credit"> (Instagram)</span></figcaption></figure>



<p>Hartsook&#8217;s case was still in the works when he and his brother allegedly pillaged Ashley Martson&#8217;s salon, Martson Hair Co. on February 1.</p>



<p>They took hair clippers, trimmers, and other tools, presumably for resale or for their metals. They stole cahs and coins from registers, and even two safes &#8212; containing $100, a gun, and &#8220;various documents.&#8221; All told, the stolen items were worth as much as $20,000 if not more. A devastating loss for her and her business.</p>



<p>It sounds like the burglars loaded the goods into trash bins and drove away in a black van. A black van not unlike the one that Hartsook allegedly used to swipe a trash bin. That is &#8230; quite the M.O. to choose when you&#8217;re already under investigation.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/05/suspected-burglar-of-ashley-martsons-salon-also-arrested-for-homicide-90-day-fiance-alum-reveals/">Suspected Burglar of Ashley Martson&#8217;s Salon Also Arrested for Homicide, 90 Day &hellip;</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/05/suspected-burglar-of-ashley-martsons-salon-also-arrested-for-homicide-90-day-fiance-alum-reveals/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ashley Martson ROBBED During Hair Salon Break-in!</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/02/ashley-martson-robbed-during-hair-salon-break-in/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/02/ashley-martson-robbed-during-hair-salon-break-in/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 16:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/?p=468195</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 4</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span>Almost two years ago, Ashley Martson and Jay Smith finalized their divorce. At last! The two had previously set a &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/02/ashley-martson-robbed-during-hair-salon-break-in/">Ashley Martson ROBBED During Hair Salon Break-in!</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 4</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span>
<p>Almost two years ago, <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/">Ashley Martson and Jay Smith finalized their divorce</a>. At last!</p>



<p>The two had previously set a <em>90 Day Fiance</em> record for breakups and reconciliations. That is, before Big Ed and Liz.</p>



<p>Ashley has moved on with her life. She is a businesswoman.</p>



<p>Unfortunately, robbers broke in and robbed her hair salon this week. Ashley is posting security video and asking the community for help.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">90 Day Fiance alum Ashley Martson took this tearful selfie on the night of her birthday party in New York after the party was crashed by her ex.</figcaption></figure>



<p>On Wednesday, February 1, Ashley Martson took to Instagram to share a security video and a plea for help.</p>



<p>&#8220;I am seeking public assistance!&#8221; she began. &#8220;Anyone in the area of Industrial highway, Do you recognize anyone in this video?&#8221;</p>



<p>Ashley wrote: &#8220;Early this morning my salon #MartsonHairCompany in East York, PA was burglarized and ransacked!&#8221; </p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"></figure>



<p>&#8220;These individuals took well over 30K in products, supplies, shears, dryers,&#8221; Ashley listed. </p>



<p>&#8220;And,&#8221; she revealed, &#8220;the safe that contained a gun.&#8221; That is so scary!</p>



<p>Ashley then asked that &#8220;Anyone with any information or knowledge please contact: Springettsbury Township Police at: 717.757.3525 or DM me. Anonymous tips will be respected! Please share this and Thank You!&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>



<p>On Thursday Morning, Ashley posted a longer post to reflect upon this crisis &#8212; and also upon some silver linings.</p>



<p>&#8220;Yesterday was trying for me. I built my salon from nothing straight out of beauty school,&#8221; she began.</p>



<p>&#8220;Now we’re at almost two years and with the help of my staff,&#8221; Ashley cited, &#8220;we turned @martsonhaircompany into a success!&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"></figure>



<p>&#8220;Somethings we spend a lot of time on at the salon is education @ethos_beauty to perfect our craft,&#8221; Ashley wrote.</p>



<p>&#8220;Countless hours working in the community,&#8221; she went on. &#8220;We’ve been to multiple hair shows for not only education but to talk with some of the best in the industry to make the salon a success.&#8221;</p>



<p>Ashley affirmed: &#8220;We are deserving of our success at the salon as we work very hard day in and day out.&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">90 Day Fiance alum Ashley Martson shared this cozy bedroom photo with her fans and followers on Instagram.</figcaption></figure>



<p>&#8220;I have cut peoples hair while wiping their tears away, I have made a bride the most beautiful woman in the world on her big day,&#8221; Ashley listed. Sometimes, a haircut is more than just a haircut.</p>



<p>&#8220;I have done hair for the deceased to make someone look nice for their final goodbye to their loved ones and this world,&#8221; she recalled. Again, that likely meant so much to a lot of surviving loved ones.</p>



<p>&#8220;I have done so much in these last two years,&#8221; Ashley wrote. &#8220;My salon, my staff and myself did not deserve what happened to us yesterday!&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>



<p>&#8220;Yes, I have insurance and everything will be replaced,&#8221; Ashley confirmed. So that much is good!</p>



<p>&#8220;What won&#8217;t be replaced is sentimental belongings,&#8221; she noted. &#8220;Such as shears that cut their child’s first haircut, a spouse who passed away belongings that meant lot to my stylist, a few other belongings of his and more!&#8221;</p>



<p>Ashley added: &#8220;On top of that, this has triggered serious ptsd in myself stemming from a robbery, rape, and kidnapping I endured at the age of 19 just a few miles from my salon.&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">90 Day Fiance: Happily Ever After? star Ashley Martson got all dolled up for a mock wedding photoshoot, and she looks stunning.</figcaption></figure>



<p>Years ago, we reported on how Ashley survived that horrible ordeal when she was just a teenager.</p>



<p>&#8220;I’ll no longer be comfortable in what is my literal dream salon!&#8221; she lamented. &#8220;Nor will my staff.&#8221;</p>



<p>Ashley added: &#8220;They stole a lot from us yesterday but not today!&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"></figure>



<p>&#8220;Today I will walk in my salon from 10-8 and work beside my amazing stylists @lady.j.hair and @love4hair13 and do what we love,&#8221; Ashley vowed.</p>



<p>&#8220;The way all my staff came running to the salon when we told them what happened almost made me cry,&#8221; she expressed.</p>



<p>&#8220;They are amazing and irreplaceable,&#8221; Ashley gushed. &#8220;You can’t stop us here @martsonhaircompany but nice try!&#8221;</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">90 Day Fiance: Happily Ever After? star Ashley Martson looks stunning in this low-cut red sundress as she gazes out into the distance.</figcaption></figure>



<p>&#8220;A special thank you to the @springettspd and the detectives for working the scene for hours yesterday very diligently and treating us so kindly!&#8221; Ashley remarked.</p>



<p>&#8220;Also, thank you so much for all the kind words and support from my community, our clients, and everyone else who reached out!&#8221; she concluded.</p>



<p>We are saddened to hear that this happened to Ashley and to her place of business.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/02/ashley-martson-robbed-during-hair-salon-break-in/">Ashley Martson ROBBED During Hair Salon Break-in!</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2023/02/ashley-martson-robbed-during-hair-salon-break-in/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>90 Day Fiance: Which Couples Are (Somehow) Still Together? Which Broke Up?</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/90-day-fiance-which-couples-are-somehow-still-together/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/90-day-fiance-which-couples-are-somehow-still-together/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 13:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Anfisa Arkhipchenko]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Angela Deem]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Colt Johnson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Elizabeth Potthast]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larissa Lima]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicole Nafziger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paola Mayfield]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/90-day-fiance-which-couples-are-somehow-still-together/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &#60; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/90-day-fiance-which-couples-are-somehow-still-together/">90 Day Fiance: Which Couples Are (Somehow) Still Together? Which Broke Up?</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &lt; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span><div class="mvt-featured-post-block"><div class="block-container"><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-couples-whos-still-together/"><div class="block-header"><div class="block-image"></div><h2 class="block-title">90 Day Fiance: Which Couples Are (Somehow) Still Together?</h2></div></a><div class="block-data"><div class="block-button"><a class="btn" href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-couples-whos-still-together/"><span>VIEW GALLERY</span><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" class="arrow-right" width="32px" height="12px" viewBox="0 0 32 12"><g transform="translate(0,12) scale(0.1,-0.1)" fill="#000000" stroke="none"><path d="M240 60 l0 -61 35 27 c19 14 35 30 35 34 0 4 -16 20 -35 34 l-35 27 0 -61z"/><path d="M4 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M84 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M164 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/></g></svg></a></div></div></div></div>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/90-day-fiance-which-couples-are-somehow-still-together/">90 Day Fiance: Which Couples Are (Somehow) Still Together? Which Broke Up?</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/90-day-fiance-which-couples-are-somehow-still-together/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>90 Day Fiance Star Wanted by Police After Barbershop Shooting</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/michael-baltimore-90-day-fiance-alum-wanted-by-police-after-barb/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/michael-baltimore-90-day-fiance-alum-wanted-by-police-after-barb/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2021 17:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jay Smith]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/michael-baltimore-90-day-fiance-alum-wanted-by-police-after-barb/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 3</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span>After literal years of buildup (and setbacks), Ashley Martson and Jay Smith finalized their divorce earlier this year. Infamously, one &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/michael-baltimore-90-day-fiance-alum-wanted-by-police-after-barb/">90 Day Fiance Star Wanted by Police After Barbershop Shooting</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 3</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span><p>After literal years of buildup (and setbacks), <a href="/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/">Ashley Martson and Jay Smith finalized their divorce</a> earlier this year.</p>
<p>Infamously, one of Jay&#8217;s many cheating incidents was revealed by his barbershop friends.</p>
<p>One of those men, whom <em>90 Day Fiance</em> viewers saw on their screens, is dead.</p>
<p>The other man is the main suspect, and police are now offering a cash reward.</p>
<p><div class="wp-block-image placeholder-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"></figure></div></p>
<p>Infamously, Jay Smith boned a random girl in the bathroom of GQ Barbershop.</p>
<p>He didn&#8217;t own the place. He didn&#8217;t even really work there.</p>
<p>The owners had generously allowed him to do some tattoo work there.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image placeholder-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"></figure></div>
<p>Kendell Cook and Michael Baltimore didn&#8217;t just tell Ashley Martson about Jay&#8217;s cheating.</p>
<p>They also showed her video evidence of Jay facing the consequences for &quot;disrespecting&quot; their establishment.</p>
<p>Namely, Jay got a little roughed up on the video.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image placeholder-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"></figure></div>
<p>Since then, tragedy has afflicted GQ Barbershop.</p>
<p>There was a shooting on the night of Saturday, May 22.</p>
<p>A man naed Anthony Lamar White was injured. Kendell Cook was killed.</p>
<div class="wp-block-image placeholder-image">
<figure class="aligncenter size-full"></figure></div>
<p>Now, Michael Anthony Baltimore is wanted by police in connection with the shooting.</p>
<p>He is currently their prime suspect.</p>
<p>According to law enforcement, he is considered both armed and dangerous.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>&quot;Crime Stoppers along with the ATF is offering a reward up to a $7000 cash for information to Crime Stoppers leading to the capture of Baltimore,&quot; a recent statement read.</p>
<p>&quot;We don&rsquo;t need your name,&quot; the release adds. &quot;We don&rsquo;t need you to come to court and testify about his crimes.&quot;</p>
<p>&quot;We want to know where he is,&quot; the statement adds, &quot;so we can peacefully arrest him.&quot;</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Law enforcement of course asks that no one approach Michael Baltimore.</p>
<p>It is very fair and wise to regard law enforcement statements with skepticism, but that, at least, is honestly good advice.</p>
<p>Even if this is all some sort of colossal misunderstanding, even innocent people can make mistakes when confronted.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Now, those of us who don&#8217;t live in or around Carlisle, Pennsylvania are pretty unlikely to spot Michael Baltimore.</p>
<p>But this is also relevant information to <em>90 Day Fiance</em> fans and viewers.</p>
<p>It is always relevant to know more about the people you see on TV.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Obviously, some details of their lives are private &#8212; that&#8217;s true of anyone &#8212; and should remain so.</p>
<p>But when people appear on reality television, fans and viewers are naturally interested in their lives.</p>
<p>And quite frankly, it never hurts to know if someone on TV is good or bad.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Not everyone is like Angela Deem &#8212; showing viewers exactly who and what they are.</p>
<p>Others, like Geoffrey Paschel, only showed red flags on camera.</p>
<p>It was only through off-camera research that fans discovered the terrible truth about what Geoffrey is really like.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1024" height="759" src="http://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte.jpg" alt="Jay Smith and Ashley Martson for 90 Day Fiance: Happily Ever After?" class="wp-image-314124" srcset="https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-300x222.jpg 300w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-768x569.jpg 768w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-735x545.jpg 735w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-335x248.jpg 335w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-347x257.jpg 347w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-520x385.jpg 520w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-640x474.jpg 640w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/11/jay-smith-and-ashley-martson-for-90-day-fiance-happily-ever-afte-960x712.jpg 960w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 760px) calc(100vw - 20px), 720px" /><figcaption>(TLC)</figcaption></figure>

<p>In other cases, like with Lisa Hamme, the show&#8217;s editors actively helped her cover up what sort of person she is.</p>
<p>At the Tell All, it was revealed that she had called her then-husband, Usman Umar, the N-word.</p>
<p>That was edited out of the Tell All that aired, and the world only learned of it because the special leaked.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/michael-baltimore-90-day-fiance-alum-wanted-by-police-after-barb/">90 Day Fiance Star Wanted by Police After Barbershop Shooting</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/07/michael-baltimore-90-day-fiance-alum-wanted-by-police-after-barb/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>90 Day Fiance Stars Whose Journeys Ended in Heartbreak</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/05/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/05/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 23:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Danielle Mullins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deavan Clegg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jorge Nava]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larissa Lima]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Youngquist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Molly Hopkins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natalie Mordovtseva]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicole Nafziger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olga Koshimbetova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rosemarie Vega]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steven Frend]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/05/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &#60; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/05/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/">90 Day Fiance Stars Whose Journeys Ended in Heartbreak</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &lt; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span><div class="mvt-featured-post-block"><div class="block-container"><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/"><div class="block-header"><div class="block-image"></div><h2 class="block-title">90 Day Fiance Cast Members Whose Journeys Ended in Heartbreak</h2></div></a><div class="block-data"><div class="block-button"><a class="btn" href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/"><span>VIEW GALLERY</span><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" class="arrow-right" width="32px" height="12px" viewBox="0 0 32 12"><g transform="translate(0,12) scale(0.1,-0.1)" fill="#000000" stroke="none"><path d="M240 60 l0 -61 35 27 c19 14 35 30 35 34 0 4 -16 20 -35 34 l-35 27 0 -61z"/><path d="M4 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M84 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M164 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/></g></svg></a></div></div></div></div>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/05/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/">90 Day Fiance Stars Whose Journeys Ended in Heartbreak</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/05/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>90 Day Fiance Cast Members Whose Journeys Ended in Heartbreak</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 23:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Danielle Mullins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Deavan Clegg]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jorge Nava]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larissa Lima]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Mike Youngquist]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Molly Hopkins]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natalie Mordovtseva]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Nicole Nafziger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olga Koshimbetova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rosemarie Vega]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steven Frend]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The smash hit series 90 Day Fiance follows couples from around the globe on their international journeys for love and &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/">90 Day Fiance Cast Members Whose Journeys Ended in Heartbreak</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The smash hit series <em>90 Day Fiance</em> follows couples from around the globe on their international journeys for love and family.</p><p>Sometimes, it&#8217;s love at first sight and it lasts forever.</p><p>Other times, it takes months of courtship and convincing for two people to realize that they&#8217;re head over heels for each other.</p><p>But other times &#8230; no matter how long it took to fall in love, or what that courtship entailed, they ultimately fall out of love.</p><p>And sometimes, the fallout is downright brutal.</p><p>Cheating, betrayals, using people for fame, manipulation. You name it. Some cast members run a gauntlet of misery.</p><p>Take a look at some of the most heartbroken stars in the franchise&#8217;s history. Think it was worth it for them?</p><figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-1 is-cropped wp-block-gallery-2 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex"><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Ashley Martson</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">1</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Jay Smith cheated on Ashley right after their wedding by downloading Tinder and chatting with an 18-year-old girl. A few months later, he cheated on her again, boning a random girl in a barbershop bathroom. A few months later, Ashley learned that he was sleeping with a mistress. Several months later, they reconciled, only to break up when a girl Jay was sleeping with (of course) claimed to be pregnant. They got back together the next year and vowed to make it work, only for Jay to once again cheat on Ashley. So not only did that story end in heartbreak, it had a lot of heartbreak along the way.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Rosemarie Vega</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">2</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Rose couldn&#8217;t have known what to expect from Big Ed Brown except, hopefully, a lot of love, a future together, and a better life for her son. Instead, he lied to her. He lied about his appearance, he shamed her over her body hair, false claims about her dental hygiene, and was weirdly insistent that she and only she take an STI test. The biggest lie, the one that broke them up forever, was his intention to have a vasectomy &#8212; something that Ed had hidden for months despite knowing that Rose wanted to have more children. She was devastated.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Danielle Mullins Jbali</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">3</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1190" height="939" data-id="356739" src="http://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears.png" alt="Danielle Mullins Jbali" class="wp-image-356739" srcset="https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears.png 1190w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-300x237.png 300w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-1024x808.png 1024w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-768x606.png 768w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-735x580.png 735w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-335x264.png 335w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-347x274.png 347w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-520x410.png 520w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-640x505.png 640w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-960x758.png 960w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2021/05/danielle-mullins-in-tears-1080x852.png 1080w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 760px) calc(100vw - 20px), 720px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(Discovery+)</figcaption></div><p>Mohamed Jbali wanted to come to America from Tunisia. Danielle Mullins wanted a hot, younger man to have sex with. They could have had a perfectly equitable exchange, except for a lot of backstabbing and insults and hurt feelings. A lot of those hurt feelings were Danielle&#8217;s. Was she using him? Of course. But it also seems like she loved him in her own way, and was devastated by their ugly divorce &#8212; to the point where, years later, she was still hung up on him.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Molly Hopkins</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">4</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Molly met Luis Mendez while she was on vacation. Despite the age gap and a lot of suspicions, they got married. But though they both had their issues and got divorced, Luis was the one who was suddenly remarrying just five months later. Molly, on the other hand, took her time before moving on. </p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Jorge Nava</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">5</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>There&#8217;s no good way to get dumped, least of all by your wife, but allegedly being ghosted while you&#8217;re in prison because your (incarceration) weight loss is getting too much attention in comparison to your wife&#8217;s social media posts is &#8230; harsh. Now, Anfisa has strongly rejected that characterization of their breakup, but Jorge didn&#8217;t exactly have a wife waiting for him when he got out of prison, and yeah, that was rough.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Larissa Lima</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">6</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>On camera, Larissa was an over-the-top dramatic woman who turned on a dime and was emotionally volatile. To some extent, sure, that&#8217;s true. But the truth is that she fell in love with a man who pursued her online &#8212; even after she blocked him a couple of times. They met up, and she was blown away when he proposed to her on their vacation. She came to the United States, leaving her family behind, to be with a man &#8230; and his mother. Larissa quickly discovered that despite Colt&#8217;s sex drive, he didn&#8217;t seem to show her affection like a normal boyfriend would, let alone a husband. After months of manipulation and being cheated on, their marriage ended in an ugly conflict, and she was left with $38 to her name. She was beyond devastated.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Nicole Nafziger</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">7</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>This one is a little enigmatic, but she invested a lot in her relationship with Azan Tefou (real name Hassan M&#8217;Raouni). She invested a lot of time, a lot of energy, and thousands of &#8230; minutes spent in contact with her fiance, even getting stuck in Morocco for five months during the COVID-19 pandemic. Then, suddenly, in early 2021, it seemed that they were no longer engaged. Nicole doesn&#8217;t have to confirm anything, and she hasn&#8217;t, but fans can only conclude that Nicole going totally radio silent (not even mentioning an engagement in her bio anymore) means that it&#8217;s over. Even if that&#8217;s good news, it sounds very sad for Nicole.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Jess Caroline</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">8</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1025" height="804" data-id="349827" src="http://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach.png" alt="Jess Caroline" class="wp-image-349827" srcset="https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach.png 1025w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-300x235.png 300w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-768x602.png 768w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-735x577.png 735w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-335x263.png 335w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-347x272.png 347w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-520x408.png 520w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-640x502.png 640w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2020/07/jess-caroline-admires-colt-johnson-on-the-beach-960x753.png 960w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 760px) calc(100vw - 20px), 720px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(TLC)</figcaption></div><p>Neither the first nor the last woman to get the Colt Johnson treatment, Jess was strung along by Colt, though he later admitted to having cheated on her throughout their entire relationship. He lied to her, cheated on her, told her that she was imagining things when she was 100% right, and then for good measure, sent pics of his dick out to a whole bunch of women before he and Jess actually ended things for good. Jess didn&#8217;t deserve that. No one does.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Amira Lollysa</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">9</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Speaking of manipulative dudes, Andrew Kenton and Amira have very different versions of who was the villain in their relationship, but some things cannot be disputed. One, that Andrew clearly piled on the pressure with Amira throughout their relationship. Two, that he added even more pressure right before her flight &#8212; he says in response to Amira getting an agent, she says that it was his insistence that she commit to having kids right away. Three, that Amira was heartbroken and tearful on camera in the aftermath.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Erika Owens</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">10</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Erika Owens and Stephanie Matto hit it off online, like so many people &#8212; particularly within the LGBTQ+ community &#8212; do. Unfortunately, they lived on opposite sides of the world, but they still committed to meet each other and, possibly, to marry. But they did not get what they expected. In particular, Stephanie had some serious insecurity issues that tore their relationship apart at the seams. Erika has moved on, but at the time, she was very hurt &#8212; with neither woman on speaking terms with the other.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Deavan Clegg</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">11</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Deavan already had enough reasons to be heartbroken when going to South Korea and finding out that Jihoon Lee had lied to trick her into going there and ending up at an unacceptable apartment with their two children. Things got much, much worse later, after cameras had mostly finished filming their season &#8212; with Jihoon accused of violent child abuse against Deavan&#8217;s daughter. Deavan fled with her children to the United States, having to suddenly figure out a new plan for her life after her dreams of a married life with Jihoon were destroyed.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Natalie Mordovtseva</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">12</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>We do not yet know the final straw that broke the marriage of Natalie and Mike, but we all know that they shouldn&#8217;t have even tied the knot. From Natalie&#8217;s perspective, Mike was a poor communicator, he dragged his heels, he was unsympathetic to her feelings and hurtfully dismissive of her concerns or any efforts to get him to commit to, well, anything. He also canceled their wedding two hours before it was supposed to happen, two days before her visa would expire, in the midst of a global pandemic.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Mike Youngquist</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">13</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>From Mike&#8217;s side of things, Natalie taunted him with cruel insults, tried to micromanage his diet, called him &#8220;low class&#8221; among other things, and to him, she felt pushy in a way that ruined moments for him. Neither of them are the good guy. Neither of them are the only villain in the relationship. Both of them were certainly heartbroken &#8212; more than once &#8212; during their ill-fated romance.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Steven Frend and Olga Koshimbetova</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">14</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>This is another weirdly enigmatic thing, because they are committed to co-parenting, even traveling to Russia together (temporarily; the rumors that they planned a permanent move to Russia were bogus). Are they together? Well, they never divorced, but they did announce a breakup in late 2020. This couple&#8217;s one real issue on camera was Steven&#8217;s toxic attitude (one learned from family, but we all sincerely hope that he no longer speaks this way), and truth be told, it was possibly fans who were most heartbroken by their breakup. A lot of people have rooted for these two and their precious baby boy.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Darcey Silva</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">15</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="486" height="445" data-id="305211" src="http://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/08/darcey-and-jesse.png" alt="Darcey Silva" class="wp-image-305211" srcset="https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/08/darcey-and-jesse.png 486w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/08/darcey-and-jesse-300x275.png 300w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/08/darcey-and-jesse-335x307.png 335w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2018/08/darcey-and-jesse-347x318.png 347w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 486px) 100vw, 486px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(TLC)</figcaption></div><p>Darcey has ended up heartbroken more than once. Jesse Meester was as narcissistic as he was handsome, and seemed to love public fights on Instagram and flirting with fans just to get a rise out of Darcey more than he ever loved his fiancee. Tom Brooks seemed similarly fascinated by becoming famous, even suspected of stringing Darcey along to appear on another season with her.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Liz Marie</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">16</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Liz thought of Big Ed Brown as just a friendly older man until he stunned the single mom by asking her out. About his daughter&#8217;s age, she never expected that, but said yes. They actually hit it off for a while &#8230; until it became clear to Liz that Ed was interested in airing all of their dirty laundry with public fights in front of cameras, no matter Liz&#8217;s feelings on the matter. He used nasty manipulation tactics on her, leading to her ditching him in Vegas and flying home, even as a single mother on a budget, because she had to get away from him.</p></figure></figure>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/">90 Day Fiance Cast Members Whose Journeys Ended in Heartbreak</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-stars-whose-journeys-ended-in-heartbreak/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ashley Martson and Jay Smith Divorce Finalized at Last! The 90 Day Fiance Nightmare is &#8230;</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 13:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jay Smith]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 4</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span>Late last year, Ashley Martson filed to divorce Jay Smith for the third time. 90 Day Fiance fans collectively held &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/">Ashley Martson and Jay Smith Divorce Finalized at Last! The 90 Day Fiance Nightmare is &hellip;</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> 4</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minutes</span></span><p>Late last year, <a href="/2020/12/ashley-martson-im-divorcing-jay-for-the-third-time/">Ashley Martson filed to divorce Jay Smith for the third time</a>.</p>
<p><em>90 Day Fiance</em> fans collectively held their breath, bracing themselves for the worst &#8212; another reconciliation.</p>
<p>But this time, something truly wonderful happened.</p>
<p>The divorce is finalized. The marriage is ended. Our long national nightmare is over at last.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p><em>Us Weekly</em> confirmed on Wednesday, March 17, that Ashley Martson and Jay Smith&#8217;s divorce was finalized.</p>
<p>Ashley made her third and final divorce filing in October fo 2020.</p>
<p>And that filing came a month after she announced their breakup on September 19.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Ashley&#8217;s initial announcement of the split did not lay the blame on either party.</p>
<p>Instead, she claimed that it was purely a consequence of her being unable to let go of the past.</p>
<p>Fans were shocked to hear her claim that Jay had, for once, not cheated on her.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Later, however, Ashley confessed that she had felt humiliated by what was now his <em>fifth </em>cheating scandal.</p>
<p>She apologized to fans for lying to them to cover for Jay&#8217;s repeated infidelity.</p>
<p>That, at least, was much less surprising for fans to hear, and sounded like the Jay they all knew.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>&quot;After&quot; this final split with Ashley, Jay publicly reunited with Kayla O&#8217;Brien, who had been his mistress in early 2019.</p>
<p>Jay would go on to date Kayla for much of 2019 until he broke up with her and got back with Ashley in secret late that summer.</p>
<p>Reports say that it was with Kayla that Jay was once again cheating in 2020 before their split.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>As we reported last year, Jay was said to be crashing at Kayla&#8217;s after Ashley kicked him out.</p>
<p>Kayla had to drive Jay over to Ashley&#8217;s house to pick up his stuff.</p>
<p>That sounds like an improvement over breaking into her house while she&#8217;s on vacation, but &#8230; deeply awkward.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>It was then reported to In Touch Weekly that &quot;Jay tried filing a PFA (Protection from Abuse) order against Ashley.&quot;</p>
<p>The source explained that this was &quot;after she filed for divorce.&quot;</p>
<p>Jay&#8217;s reason was said to be &quot;because that&#8217;s the only way he can stay in the US.&quot;</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Jay does not have a green card.</p>
<p>He has long feared divorce as he could be deported back to Jamaica at any time.</p>
<p>The attempt to secure the order was ultimately dropped by the court.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Professionally, however, Jay was still working out of &quot;his&quot; tattoo shop.</p>
<p>This is the one that Ashley helped him open last year (during the pandemic; why?!) to make his dreams come true.</p>
<p>Ashley told fans that she was working to get it transferred to his name.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>What she didn&#8217;t tell fans is that, reportedly, the tattoo shop was losing her a tremendous amount of money.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s hard to imagine opening a tattoo parlor in the summer of 2020 to be a profitable venture.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s a little like having your grand opening of a restaurant be April 1 2020. Bad timing, no matter the product.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>

<p>Of course, while the rest of the world sees Jay for who he is, he has one ardent defender.</p>
<p>Kayla O&#8217;Brien, even though he dropped her at the drop of a hat to get back with Ashley in the summer of 2019, is on his side.</p>
<p>She has publicly denied that Jay cheated with her (this time), claiming that Ashley was &quot;toxic&quot; and &quot;draining his spirit.&quot;</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Kayla also claimed that Jay had broken up with Ashley, that he hadn&#8217;t cheated.</p>
<p>She claimed that he sent Ashley a lengthy message on why <em>he </em>wanted to end things, and was &quot;gentle&quot; about it.</p>
<p>Of course, Kayla&#8217;s ideas about how that marriage ended likely came from Jay.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"></figure>
<p>Jay himself has gone on to tell <a href="https://www.intouchweekly.com/posts/90-day-fiance-ashley-martson-and-jay-smiths-divorce-details/"><em>In Touch Weekly</em></a> that he &quot;doesn&#8217;t believe in marriage&quot; and doesn&#8217;t plan on remarrying.</p>
<p>We won&#8217;t insult anyone&#8217;s intelligence by asking why he married Ashley, then.</p>
<p>He&#8217;s not interested in remarriage because it&#8217;s unlikely to give him legal residency at this point. We all knew what he thought about marriage.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/">Ashley Martson and Jay Smith Divorce Finalized at Last! The 90 Day Fiance Nightmare is &hellip;</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/ashley-martson-and-jay-smith-divorce-finalized-at-last-the-90-da/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Most GORGEOUS 90 Day Fiance Ladies of All Time!</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 23:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amira Lollysa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brittany Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chantel Everett]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erika Owens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evelin Villegas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fernanda Flores]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jess Caroline]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Julia Trubkina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Juliana Custodio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kalani Faagata]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larissa Lima]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Melyza Zeta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natalie Mordovtseva]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olga Koshimbetova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paola Mayfield]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stephanie Matto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tania Maduro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yara Zaya]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &#60; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/">The Most GORGEOUS 90 Day Fiance Ladies of All Time!</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &lt; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span><div class="mvt-featured-post-block"><div class="block-container"><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/"><div class="block-header"><div class="block-image"></div><h2 class="block-title">90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Female Cast Members of All Time!</h2></div></a><div class="block-data"><div class="block-button"><a class="btn" href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/"><span>VIEW GALLERY</span><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" class="arrow-right" width="32px" height="12px" viewBox="0 0 32 12"><g transform="translate(0,12) scale(0.1,-0.1)" fill="#000000" stroke="none"><path d="M240 60 l0 -61 35 27 c19 14 35 30 35 34 0 4 -16 20 -35 34 l-35 27 0 -61z"/><path d="M4 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M84 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M164 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/></g></svg></a></div></div></div></div>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/">The Most GORGEOUS 90 Day Fiance Ladies of All Time!</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Female Cast Members of All Time!</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 23:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Amira Lollysa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brittany Banks]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chantel Everett]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Erika Owens]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evelin Villegas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fernanda Flores]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jess Caroline]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Julia Trubkina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Juliana Custodio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kalani Faagata]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larissa Lima]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Melyza Zeta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Natalie Mordovtseva]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olga Koshimbetova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Paola Mayfield]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rosemarie Vega]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stephanie Matto]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tania Maduro]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yara Zaya]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Viewers come to TLC&#8217;s smash hit 90 Day Fiance for a lot of reasons, just like the couples do. Some &#8230;</p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/">90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Female Cast Members of All Time!</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Viewers come to TLC&#8217;s smash hit 90 Day Fiance for a lot of reasons, just like the couples do.</p><p>Some are there for the possibility of scams, the culture shock, the drama, the big personalities.</p><p>Others are there to see true love stories play out in the face of adversity.</p><p>Of course &#8230; some of the viewers find that they get a little more than that from the show.</p><p>Namely? Some of the stars are drop-dead gorgeous.</p><p>That&#8217;s no surprise, really &#8211; good looks and entertainment are often intertwined, on reality TV and beyond.</p><p>So take a look below at some of the most jaw-droppingly gorgeous ladies of 90 Day Fiance.</p><p>And don&#8217;t miss a few <strong>honorable mentions</strong> at the end &#8211; ladies who aren&#8217;t stars, but still made the list.</p><figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-1 is-cropped wp-block-gallery-4 is-layout-flex wp-block-gallery-is-layout-flex"><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Yara Zaya</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">1</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Yara knows that she&#8217;s a total knockout. This woman is distractingly gorgeous in every moment that she appears on screen.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Juliana Custodio</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">2</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Easily one of the most beautiful stars in the franchise&#8217;s history, the only downside to this young Brazilian model&#8217;s storyline was a remarkable lack of drama. Few had the gall to complain &#8212; no moment with Juliana on screen was wasted.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Brittany Banks</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">3</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>This rapper and model&#8217;s now-former fiance was said to be &#8220;obsessed&#8221; with her body, even describing it when asked what he loved about her. While that&#8217;s not really what &#8220;love&#8221; means to most people, Brittany will turn heads in any country that she visits.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Fernanda Flores</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">4</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Coming to the US with her noticeably older fiance at just 19, Fernanda was an aspiring model and already had the looks for the role. These days, she&#8217;s living and dating in Chicago while modeling, and she has only gotten more stunning.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Chantel Everett</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">5</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" width="1224" height="803" data-id="327925" src="http://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera.png" alt="Chantel Everett" class="wp-image-327925" srcset="https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera.png 1224w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-300x197.png 300w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-1024x672.png 1024w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-768x504.png 768w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-735x482.png 735w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-335x220.png 335w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-347x228.png 347w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-520x341.png 520w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-640x420.png 640w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-960x630.png 960w, https://cdn.thehollywoodgossip.com/uploads/2019/04/chantel-addresses-the-camera-1080x709.png 1080w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 760px) calc(100vw - 20px), 720px" /><figcaption class="wp-element-caption">(TLC)</figcaption></div><p>The Family Chantel is the franchise&#8217;s first-ever spinoff of its kind, focusing upon specific people rather than a premise, and most of that was prompted by the absolute chaos personified in Chantel and Pedro&#8217;s respective families. Some of that, however, came from the fact that the show&#8217;s titular star is easy on the eyes.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Evelin Villegas</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">6</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>When Corey Rathgeber went surfing off the coast of Engebao, Ecuador, he never could have imagined that he would meet the love of his life. Evelin is incredibly gorgeous, and it is no surprise that &#8212; despite the outrageous amount of hate sent her way &#8212; she has a large online following, including no shortage of subscribers on OnlyFans.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Julia Trubkina</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">7</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Did we have to use this photo? No. Did we use it anyway? Yes. Julia is an accomplished young woman who has held many jobs over the years before her future in-laws treated her like an indentured servant on their farm. You can see why she was so successful as a nightclub dancer in Russia, however, because she is cute, has an incredible body, and doesn&#8217;t see a need to hide it. Brandon once told her that she looks like his future wife &#8212; and the entire world can see why.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Rosemarie Vega</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">8</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Big Ed Brown put Rose through the wringer with a series of cruel lies and some even crueler behavior. But being on 90 Day Fiance catapulted Rose&#8217;s life forward in ways that she had not imagined. She is now working as a model, and is able to lift not only her but her family out of the abject poverty in which they were living during her season.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Kalani Faagata</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">9</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Her smile can light up a whole room, and we&#8217;re just a little too respectful to comment on what her plunging necklines can do to that some room once the lights are on. Kalani is a radiant beauty and a fan favorite for good reason.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Jess Caroline</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">10</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Unfortunate enough to run afoul of Colt Johnson and his endless lust, Jess is a Brazilian model who was living and working in the US before they met. She is just as cute as a button. After Colt, she had no problem finding someone who actually loved and respected her without cheating.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Anfisa Arkhipchenko Nava</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">11</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Anfisa came to the US from Russia to be with Jorge. Things did not work out. Frankly, they were never going to. Anfisa&#8217;s beauty turned heads, and when she devoted herself to transforming her body, she won awards at her very first bikini bodybuilding competition.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Paola Mayfield</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">12</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>This fitness model is wildly hot, of course &#8212; it&#8217;s part of her job. At times, her hotness and career made her husband uncomfortable, but Russ has mellowed out somewhat.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Olga Koshimbetova</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">13</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Olga is a natural beauty. She is a photographer, but many fans like her photos most when her camera is pointed at her &#8212; and you can see why.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Loren Brovarnik</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">14</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Loren isn&#8217;t only a fan-favorite for her looks, but she is a gorgeous young woman &#8212; and now a mother.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Ashley Martson</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">15</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>There&#8217;s a reason that Ashley was able to land a man more than a decade her junior. She&#8217;s a beauty, even after having her heart broken so many times.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Larissa Lima</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">16</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Both before and after her cosmetic surgery makeovers, Larissa was a beauty. The self-styled queen now has a body that is much more like what she wants to look like, and that&#8217;s what matters. Also, she has a small army of admirers &#8212; fans who don&#8217;t just love her, but love to watch her show off her body, on Instagram and OnlyFans alike.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Melyza Zeta</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">17</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Melyza got a lot of flak for not smiling as much as fans might have liked, but it gave her this amazing Wednesday Addams energy that some of us enjoyed. Melyza is also, simply put, beautiful.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Amira Lollysa</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">18</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>We cannot explain all of Amira&#8217;s choices, but this French woman of Egyptian descent is a true beauty.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Tania Maduro</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">19</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Could we have chosen a different photo of Tania? Yes &#8212; she is beautiful in so many pictures. Did we go with this one anyway? Yes, and you are very welcome. Tania is a good person, but it&#8217;s good to remember what a knockout she is.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Erika Owens</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">20</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Erika&#8217;s hair is as colorful as her personality. She&#8217;s a beautiful young Australian woman who lets her true self shine, and it&#8217;s no wonder that she was able to move on after her on-screen romance didn&#8217;t turn out so well.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Karine Martins</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">21</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Karine&#8217;s life has been difficult &#8212; both before and after meeting Paul, and for different reasons &#8212; but she is a beautiful young woman who is now the mother of two.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Deavan Clegg</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">22</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Deavan is a model who puts her two children first &#8212; even when it sees her bombarded with hate and vitriol. She is also a beautiful woman and a professional model.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Stephanie Davison</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">23</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Many fans are appalled by how gleefully production continued to film Stephanie on vacation, when she appeared intoxicated, and especially in the aftermath of her sexual assault. None of what happened in Belize changes that Stephanie is a beautiful woman who lives her life on her own terms. And yes, she&#8217;s a cougar.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Tiffany Franco</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">24</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Tiffany&#8217;s relationship has had ups and downs on screen, but she always puts her kids first. Fans admire her for that. A close second when it comes to praising Tiffany, however, is her beauty. She is so lovely.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Natalie Mordovtseva</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">25</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Despite some unflattering comparisons and some backlash over her on-screen behavior, Natalie is a beautiful woman with piercing eyes.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Stephanie Matto</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">26</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Her relationship didn&#8217;t work out, largely due to her own behavior, but Stephanie is an absolute knockout. Critics are unanimous in noting that Stephanie gives her OnlyFans subscribers the best &#8220;bang&#8221; for their buck, and has seen success on the adult media site for years. That&#8217;s not a coincidence &#8212; she&#8217;s hot, and she knows what she&#8217;s doing.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Kirlyam Cox</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">27</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Kirlyam and Alan got their happily ever after in real life after leaving the show and remain fan favorites, but it&#8217;s worth mentioning that Kirlyam is a real beauty. We stan a cute nerd!</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Honorable Mention: Kolini Faagata</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">28</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Kalani&#8217;s sister Kolini turns heads every time that she appears on screen.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Honorable Mention: Nicole Jimeno</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">29</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Despite being sometimes characterized as &#8220;Pedro&#8217;s evil sister,&#8221; Nicole is a true beauty. Well, on the outside.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Honorable Mention: Wish Shibre</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">30</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Biniyam Shibre&#8217;s sister, Wish, is gorgeous. Fans just wish that she weren&#8217;t constantly threatening babies with hellfire.</p></figure><figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><h2>Last But Not Least: Shaun Robinson</h2><div class="gallery-index-container"><div class="gallery-index">31</div></div><hr><div class="gallery-image-container"></div><p>Shaun, the 90 Day Fiance host, is older than many of the castmembers whom she interviews, but she is nothing if not STUNNING. We are looking respectfully, ma&#8217;am.</p><div class="thg-ad-wrapper"><div class="mv_slot_target" data-slot="content"></div></div></figure></figure>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/">90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Female Cast Members of All Time!</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/the-most-gorgeous-90-day-fiance-ladies-of-all-time/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Couples in Franchise History</title>
		<link>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/</link>
					<comments>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Simon Delott]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 15:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[90 Day Fiance]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Alexei Brovarnik]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ashley Martson]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Asuelu Pulaa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Brandon Gibbs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chantel Everett]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Corey Rathgeber]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Eric Nichols]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Evelin Villegas]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fernanda Flores]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jovi Dufren]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Julia Trubkina]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kalani Faagata]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Larissa Lima]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Loren Brovarnik]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Olga Koshimbetova]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Pedro Jimeno]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Steven Frend]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Yara Zaya]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p><span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &#60; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/">90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Couples in Franchise History</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<span class="span-reading-time rt-reading-time" style="display: block;"><span class="rt-label rt-prefix">Reading Time: </span> <span class="rt-time"> &lt; 1</span> <span class="rt-label rt-postfix">minute</span></span><div class="mvt-featured-post-block"><div class="block-container"><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/"><div class="block-header"><div class="block-image"></div><h2 class="block-title">90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Couples in Franchise History Revealed!</h2></div></a><div class="block-data"><div class="block-button"><a class="btn" href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/slideshows/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/"><span>VIEW GALLERY</span><svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" class="arrow-right" width="32px" height="12px" viewBox="0 0 32 12"><g transform="translate(0,12) scale(0.1,-0.1)" fill="#000000" stroke="none"><path d="M240 60 l0 -61 35 27 c19 14 35 30 35 34 0 4 -16 20 -35 34 l-35 27 0 -61z"/><path d="M4 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M84 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/><path d="M164 69 c-10 -17 13 -36 27 -22 12 12 4 33 -11 33 -5 0 -12 -5 -16 -11z"/></g></svg></a></div></div></div></div>
<p><a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/">90 Day Fiance: The Hottest Couples in Franchise History</a> was originally published on <a href="https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com">The Hollywood Gossip</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.thehollywoodgossip.com/2021/03/90-day-fiance-the-hottest-couples-in-franchise-history/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
